Preliminary Guide to the Howard W. Hallman papers, 1945-2003 MS2283
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Publication: People who care: making housing work for the poor, 1980 August (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Publication: Political and administrative decentralization of municipal government in Boston [1/3], 1969 June 12 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Publication: Political and administrative decentralization of municipal government in Boston [2/3], 1969 June 12 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Publication: Political and administrative decentralization of municipal government in Boston [3/3], 1969 June 12 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Publication: Political and administrative decentralization of municipal government in Boston vol II [1/2], 1969 June 12 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Publication: Political and administrative decentralization of municipal government in Boston vol II [2/2], 1969 June 12 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Publication: Professional values and bureaucratic behavior: the New York City Department of Health revisted, 1974 September (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Publication: Profiles of participation a workbook on citizen organization and action, 1979 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Publication: A profile of revitalization projects being implemented by neighborhood development organizations, 1981 September (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Publication: A proposal for a community-centered demonstration and research project aimed at the control of maladaptive behavior among juveniles, 1957 January (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Publication: Proposal for citizen involvement project, 1975 April 30 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Publication: Recommendations city government in the community state charter revisions Commission for New York city, 1975 February 5 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Publication: The rich get richer and the poor write proposals, 1978 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Publication: Services inventory Greater Homewood Community Corporation, 1974 November 8 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Publication: Toward research on community action agencies: key variables and research instruments, 1966 October (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Publication: Urbabble, 1980 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Publication: Youthbook models and resources for neighborhood use, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Social issues 1960's "Riots" Commission, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Social issues 1960's Watts, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Social issues 1960's Food, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Social issues 1960's Juvenile Deliquency, undated (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Social issues 1960's Social Planning, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Social issues 1960's Race, 1963-1969 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Social issues 1960's Negro Family, undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Social issues 1960's White House conference "To fulfill these rights" planning session, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Social issues 1960's White House conference "To fulfill these rights", 1965 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Social issues 1960's Civil Rights Organizations, undated (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Zagreb conference on citizen particpation [1/3], 1971 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Zagreb conference on citizen particpation [2/3], 1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Zagreb conference on citizen particpation [3/3], 1971 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Resident participation, 1967-1969 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman Outline general book on citizen participation, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: community action, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: Community action in North Carolina: an overview of the North Carolina fund project, 1964-1967 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: Involvement of the poor article, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: Model cities, undated (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: Independent citizen action, undated (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: Partnership and Neighborhood Control, undated (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: Little City Halls, undated (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: Headquarters vs. Field, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: A Look Ahead, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: Neighborhood Centers "book", undated (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: Hallman's Screwball, undated (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: Teaching, undated (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: What You Say Is What You Are, undated (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Citizen participation 1968 notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: Ideas for article, speeches, undated (Box 31, Folder 16)
- the Reformer, 1970 Notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: Social reform, undated (Box 31, Folder 17)
- the Reformer, 1970 Notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: The Reformer: Prologue, undated (Box 31, Folder 18)
- the Reformer, 1970 Notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: The Reformer: Working from the Outside, undated (Box 31, Folder 19)
- the Reformer, 1970 Notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: The Reformer: Gaining Control, undated (Box 31, Folder 20)
- the Reformer, 1970 Notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: The Reformer: Governing, undated (Box 31, Folder 21)
- the Reformer, 1970 Notes for a book never written by Howard Hallman: The Reformer: Bibliography, undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Book on community action, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Book on citizen participation, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
- After Protest by Howard W. Hallman [1/2], 1966 June (Box 32, Folder 3)
- After Protest by Howard W. Hallman [2/2], 1966 June (Box 32, Folder 4)
- It Takes Money to Live by Howard W. Hallman, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Urban Solutions-- First Draft (typed), undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Urban book -- drafts, extra copies, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Neighborhood Decentralization, 1976 May-June (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Government: Our Servant, We Its Master, undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
- These truths we hold the place and limits of government in american society, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Hallman's writings: Hallman, planning with the poor, 1964 December - 1965 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Hallman's writings: NACO position papers, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Hallman's writings: Hallman, Whither the Community Action Program, 1966 July (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Hallman's writings: Hallman, Neighborhood Boards Community Corporations, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Hallman's writings: House Hearing, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Hallman's writings: Hallman [memos] of HUD, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Hallman's writings: Hallman articles (mostly CAI), 1979-1982 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Hallman's writings: Neighborhood Governance, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Hallman's writings: Speech material, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Hallman's writings: Hallman's writings, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Hallman's writings: Urban Strategies, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Other authors: Alinsky, undated (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Other authors: Cohen, Rick, undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Other authors: The Struggle of the American Urbident for Freedom and Power [1/2], 1967 August (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Other authors: The Struggle of the American Urbident for Freedom and Power [2/2], 1967 August (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Other authors: neighborhood communtiy foundation (Milton Kotler's memos), undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Other authors: Kotler, Milton, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Other authors: Quarterly Report, 1981 February 25 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Other authors: Mudd, John, 1975 May (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Other authors: Citizen Participation, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Other authors: Shalala, Donna, Neighborhood Governments, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Other authors: Reagan Task Force, 1980 November 17 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Neighborhood Organizing and Organizations: Block Organizations, undated (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Neighborhood Organizing and Organizations: Block Organizing -- New York, undated (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Neighborhood Organizing and Organizations: Homes Associations, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Neighborhood Organizing and Organizations: Handbook for Neighborhood Organizations, undated (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Neighborhood Organizing and Organizations: Neighborhood Assistance -- Portland, OR, undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Neighborhood Organizing and Organizations: Neighborhood Assistance -- Salem, OR, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Neighborhood Organizing and Organizations: Neighborhood Assistance -- Tacoma, undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Neighborhood Organizing and Organizations: Neighborhood Organizations, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Neighborhood Organizing and Organizations: Neighborhood Organizations, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Neighborhood Organizing and Organizations: Neighborhood Organizations -- Management, undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Neighborhood Organizing and Organizations: Volunteers, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Neigh. Governance: Little City Halls -- Los Angeles, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Neigh. Governance: Neighborhood Government, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Neigh. Governance: Neigh. Management, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Neigh. Governance: Neighborhood power/control, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Neigh. Governance: Neighborhood Service Center -- Baltimore, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Neigh. Governance: Service Delivery, undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Neigh. Governance: Service Standards, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Neighborhood Legislation: Charter Language and Ordinances, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Neighborhood Legislation: National Association of Neighborhoods handbook of state and local neighborhood legislation, 1978 January (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Neighborhood Legislation: Legislation State, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Neighborhood Legislation: State Neighborhood Legislation ACIR, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Neighborhood Legislation: Legislation Federal, undated (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Neighborhood Legislation: President-Elect Reagan's Neighborhood Advisory Group, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Neighborhood Councils in 1980s: Neighborhood Councils, 1980-1981 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Neighborhood Councils in 1980s: Eugene, Oregon Neighborhood Decentralization, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Neighborhood Councils in 1980s: Honolulu Neighborhood Government, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Neighborhood Councils in 1980s: Portland, Oregon Neighborhood Decentralization, undated (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Neighborhood Councils in 1980s: St. Paul, Minnesota, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Neighborhood Councils in 1980s: Salem, Oregon, undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Birmingham, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Fort Wayne, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Washington, D.C., undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Guilford County, undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Honolulu, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Kansas City, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Lincoln, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Milwaukie, Oregon, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Minneapolis, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Newton, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Pittsburgh, undated (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Portland, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: St. Paul, undated (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Salem, undated (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Seattle, undated (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Neighborhood Councils - 1976 City Reports: Neighborhood Decentralization, undated (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Publications: The Regionalist Papers: Toward Metropolitan Unity, 1974 April (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Publications: Recommendataions Coterminality of Services in Community District, 1975 January 30 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1965-69: Speeches, 1960-1964 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1965-69: Writings, Reports (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1965-69: NACO report (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1965-69: Writings, reports, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1965-69: Human Resource Administration New York, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1965-69: Writings, Reports, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1965-69: Writings, Reports, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1965-69: Writings, Reports, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1970-77: Public Administration 246 GW, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1970-77: Watts Labor Community Action Committee, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1970-77: South East Alabama Self-help Assoc., 1973 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1970-77: New Jersey Coastal Planning, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1970-77: PAR article: local Federalism, undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Consulting reports, other writings 1970-77: Neighborhood Commission ideas, 1976-1977 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Neighborhoods PAC, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 12)
- HUD paper Neighborhood governance by Howard W. Hallman, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Neighborhood Assistance Program, 1982-1983 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Unfounded proposals, undated (Box 41, Folder 3)
- President's Committee on Juvenile Deliquency, 1961-1964 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- President's Committee on Juvenile Deliquency: New Haven Youth Development Program Part I through Part IV, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- President's Committee on Juvenile Deliquency: A proposal for the prevention and control of deliquency by expanding opportunties, 1961-1962 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- President's Committee on Juvenile Deliquency: Youth in the ghetto a study of the consequences of powerlessness, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Metro: Metropolitan Government - Philadelphia proposals, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Metro: Metro writings, undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Metro: Suburban Model, undated (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Local Gov't Reform: City Council, undated (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Local Gov't Reform: Local government reform task force report, undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Local Gov't Reform: Inter-governmental relations, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Local Gov't Reform: Advisory Neighborhood Councils Washington, DC, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Newsletters, 1970's -80's: Citizen Participation, 1979-1981 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Newsletters, 1970's -80's: Citizen Participation, 1981-1983 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Newsletters, 1970's -80's: Southern Neighbors, 1979-1984 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Newsletters, 1970's -80's: Urban Resources, 1983-1984 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Newsletters, 1970's -80's: Rain, 1976-1982 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Newsletters, 1970's -80's: Rain, 1982-1984 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Newsletters, 1970's -80's: Self-Reliance, 1977-1981 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Newsletters, 1970's -80's: Shelter Force, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Philadelphia housing policy - city, 1955 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Philadelphia Housing Assn., undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Philadelphia Housing Assn. -forum, undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Housing law, 1954-1955 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Housing - misc., undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Relocation, 1959-1967 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Adm. organization for renewal, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Housing and social structure, 1952-1964 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Housing yearbook, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Phildadelphia urban renewal, 1955-1958 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Phila. Housing Assn. - Issues, 1952-1957 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA Comprehensive governmental reorganization a proposal for the Philadelphia region by Howard Hallman, 1956 April 23 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA Metropolitan government for Philadelphia: a proposal by Howard W. Hallman, 1953 December 23 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Public Housing working papers [1/2], 1956 September (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Public Housing working papers [2/2], 1956 September (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Housing Ass. Story, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Philadelphia urban renewal, 1957-1959 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Philadelphia, PA 1952-58: Public Housing and Mrs. McGee by Elizabeth Wood, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Middle Ground Prog. New Haven 1959-61: Middle Ground Program (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Middle Ground Prog. New Haven 1959-61: Middle Ground Program, 1960-1961 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Middle Ground Prog. New Haven 1959-61: New Haven urban renewal (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: Origin of Community Progress, Inc., 1968 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: Opening opportunities New Haven's comprehensive program for community progress., 1967 April (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: Basic documents, 1961-1964 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. Howard Hallman oral history conducted by Noel A. Cazenava, 1992 April 18 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  "Transcript of a telephone interview with Howard Hallman by Noel A. Cazenava, University of Connecticut on August 18, 1992 regarding the origins of Community Progress, Inc. 46 pages. This is part of his study of social scientists involved in precursors to the U.S. War on Poverty. We covered a lot of ground. I offered naunces and background information that was not included in Russell Murphy's book on CPI Political Entrepreneurs and Urban Poverty (Heath Lexington Books, 1971)". [note written by Howard Hallman)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: Poverty and blight in New Haven, 1964 December 23 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: New Schools for New Haven, 1961 March (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI pamphlets about and press clippings, 1964-1965 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI New Haven, 1962-1965 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: Community Progress, Inc. First annual program review for the Ford Foundation [1/2], 1962-1963 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: Community Progress, Inc. First annual program review for the Ford Foundation [2/2], 1962-1963 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: Community Progress, Inc. publications, 1964-1965 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: Community Progress, Inc. publications, 1966-1968 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI five years of human renewal, 1967 June 8 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI files, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: A blueprint for better education in New Haven, 1961 October (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI first CAP grant proposal, 1964 November (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI youth development - 1st annual report, 1964 April 15 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: Report of evaluation of unified social services demonstration program, 1967 August (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: article on New Haven program, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI papers, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI newsletter, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: Program outline (completed), 1964 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI Res. Part., 1965-1967 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI complaint, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: New Haven Manpower, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: Research, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: Administration, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI files, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI documents, undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Cities where Hallman worked: Community Progress, Inc. New Haven 1962-68: CPI annual reports, 1963-1965 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- neigh. - Physical - Group Homes, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
- neigh. - Physical - Historic preservation, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- neigh. - Physical - Neigh. housing and development organizations, 1977 January (Box 50, Folder 3)
- neigh. - Physical - housing rehabilitation, 1978 March (Box 50, Folder 4)
- neigh. - Physical - neighborhood change, circa 1976 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- neigh. - Physical - behavioral foundations of neighbhorhood change, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- neigh. - Physical - neighborhood planning, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- neigh. - Physical - neighborhood reinvestment, 1976-1979 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- neigh. - Physical - neighborhood zoning, 1972-1975 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- neigh. - Physical -planning advocacy, 1965-1972 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Neighborhood Topics: bibliographies, 1982 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Neighborhood Topics: citizen surveys, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 2)